Well...
じゃーん...
Yes, Natsumi-san, it's been a while.
はい、夏美さん、久しぶり
It's been a long time.
お久しぶりです
How have you been?
元気だった?
fine.
元気
Dargi.
だるぎ
Dargi, Esset.
だるぎ、エッセットで
I feel really tired.
めっちゃだるぎじゃん
Have you thought about going to a convenience store?
コンビニでも行こうと思ったの?
No, no, this is it...
いやいや、これがもう...
It's room wear.
部屋着です
I ended up wearing it as my loungewear.
部屋着で着ちゃったんだよ
But it seems like it's okay for a little while.
でもなんか、ちょっとしたところには大丈夫そうですね
Because it's a convenience store.
コンビニだから
Well, I guess so...
いや、まぁそうだけど...
That's true, but I think you should dress up a bit.
それはそうだけど、なんかちょっとおめかししたほうがいいん
Isn't it?
じゃない ですか
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
Because she's a girl.
女の子なんだから
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
Yes, then today...
はい、じゃあ今日はね...
Look, Natsumi-chan said the other day that she was coming over for the first time in a while...
ほら、この間の夏美ちゃんが、久々に来るよって言ったから...
I was thinking about what I should do.
何やろうかなって思って考えたんですよ
Well, I've done this before, but
で、ちょっとこれは前もやったんだけど、
I received requests from everyone,
みなさんからですね、 リクエストをもらって、
This is a project to have you respond to that request.
そのリクエストに答えていただきましょうという企画なんですよ
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Why did you secretly take the request?
なんで、リクエストをね、密かに取ったんです
Mr. Koi.
小井さん
I'll be announcing now why and what kind of requests I'm getting.
なんで、どんなリクエストが来てるのかなっていうのを今から発表
So, I don't have a good or bad opinion about it.
する んで、 それ について、ちょっといいとか悪いとか嫌だ
Or, it can't be done or it can be done.
とか、 それはできないとかできるとか、
I'd like to have a little talk about various things.
い ろいろちょっとトークをね、したいんですよ
By the way, the total number of requests is
ち なみにリクエスト総数がですね、
28,975 pieces.
28975件
There are a lot of them, aren't there?
めちゃめちゃあるじゃないですか
Well, it's just a joke.
いや、まあネタなんですけどね
So, I'm going to read some of that stuff now.
なので、まあちょっとそういうのを今から読んでいきます
Well, I'm sure a lot of them are coming.
まあ、いっぱい確かに来てるんで、
Actually.
実際にね
However, there are still some things that are covered,
ただ、その中でやっぱり被ってるものとかもあるから、
That kind of thing is a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit of a bit,
そういうのはちょっと端折ってまとめちゃったりとかしてるんで、
We will make an announcement.
発表していきます
First, let's start with this one, which has a slightly smaller number of cases.
まずね、この、ちょっと件数が少ないところからいきますね
First up is the Situation series.
まずは、シチュエーションシリーズ
Well, it's a setting.
まあ、設定だよね
I've been receiving requests for things like what settings should be used.
どういう設定がいいか、みたいなのがリクエストが一応来てる
Yes, it is.
んです よ
First of all, there was something called a virtual date.
まず、第一、バーチャルデートっていうのが来てましたね
It seems like it's a virtual date with Toriso.
鳥相さんとバーチャルデートらしいです
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
But it's raining today and I'm feeling sluggish.
でもさ、今日雨降ってるし、だるぎだし
No, I don't mind this at all...
いや、私はこれでも全然...
We're going on a convenience store date.
コンビニデートするじゃん
I go to concerts many times.
コンデートに何回も行くんですよ
I'll go anywhere.
どこでも行きますよ
Well, please go on a virtual date like that.
まあ、そういうバーチャルデートをしてくださいとかね
After that, it became a hot spring trip.
あとはね、温泉旅行ってなりましたね
There's nothing I can do about this now,
これはね、もう今からどうしようもないんで、
It's a bit Hakka, but the hot springs are nice.
ちょっと客家ですけど、でも温泉いいよね
nice.
いいね
That's good.
いいよね
But look, uncle, there are circumstances that prevent us from going to the hot springs.
でもほら、おじさん、温泉行けない事情があるから
Oh, just a little.
ああ、ちょっとね
Yes, this is also Hakka.
うん、これも客家かな
This is no good either.
ダメですね、これもね
Then, after that, what is this?
それから、そのあと、なんだこれは
I feel like a lover.
恋人気分
That's during the play.
それはプレイの中ですよね
I wonder what it's like, I feel like a lover.
どうなんだろうね、恋人気分
Is it like we should flirt somehow?
なんかイチャイチャしろみたいなことなのかな?
Yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうん
copper?
どう?
yes?
そう?
When it comes to my boyfriend, I don't flirt at all.
恋人だと私、全然イチャイチャしないですよ、
real.
本当の
Ah, that's right.
あっ、そうなんだ
Well, let's take it easy.
じゃあ、サラッと
Yeah, really.
うん、本当に
Well then, cuckoo.
じゃあ、キャッコ
You can play pseudo-lover, though.
疑似恋人プレイならできますけど
What is pseudo-lover play?
疑似恋人プレイってどんなの?
Um, speaking of some kind of lover play,
あの、なんか恋人プレイっていうと、
It's not a situation where a girl would actually have a boyfriend.
女の子が実際に彼氏にしてるようなシチュエーションじゃない
Is it?
ですか
However, I am a little different.
だ けど、私はちょっと違うんで、
It's like a flirty lover's play.
イチャイチャ系の恋人プレイみたいな
Oh, are you telling me not to mess with you?
あ、てめふざけんなよとか言うの?
I'll say it.
言いますね
Ah, that kind of lover play might be good.
あ、それ、そういう恋人プレイいいかもね
vice versa.
逆に
Hey, what are you doing?
てめ、何やってんだよ
Will that be a lover's play?
それ、恋人プレイになりますか?
Just in case, there are some campers like that, right?
一応ね、そういうカンプルもいるじゃないですか
Fair enough.
まあまあ
It's called Kanpur, where women are strong.
女性が強いカンプルって言いますから
That's true.
それはそれでありですよ
I think it's a lover's play in many ways.
いろんな意味での恋人プレイってことじゃないですかね
Well, if that's the case,
まあ、でもそういうくらいだったらね、
It seems like something can be done.
なんかできそうですよね
Isn't it okay to become an old man and a masochist?
おじさんドMになればいいんでしょ?
Yeah, yeah.
そうそうそう
That's what it means.
そういうことだよね
Just in case, I said about three things related to that situation.
一応ね、そういうシチュエーション的なことが3つほど言いました
But.
けど
For now, the virtual date and hot spring trip have been rejected.
と りあえず、バーチャルデートと温泉旅行は却下ということ
That's right.
ですね
Well, the feeling of being a lover depends a little on what happens after this.
まあ、 恋人気分はちょっとこの後の流れ次第ということですね
Well then, next.
では、次
Abnormal request.
異常リクエスト
This one came a lot.
これはね、結構来てましたね
Oh, is that a cosplay?
ああ、そういうのコスプレ?
Well, it's more like cosplay or what to wear.
まあ、コスプレっていうか何を着るかみたいな
As expected, look, darugi...
さすがにほら、ね、だるぎ...
See you then.
じゃあさ
Where did you drop the good girl?
どこにいい子落としてたの?
roughly.
大体
On the other hand, it's like having sex while we're relaxing at night in this house.
逆に、この家で夜のんびりしてるところにセックスするみたいな
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうなんだ
Ah, but hey, he's coming.
あ、でもね、来てます
surely.
確かに
Um, just a request.
あの、一応リクエスト
There's something called Shifuku Fudangi.
しふくふだんぎっていうのが来てるんで
Isn't this a futongi?
これしふくふだんぎじゃん?
Look, I could request one more.
ほら、もう1個リクエストできました、
this.
これ
Shifuku fudangi.
しふくふだんぎ
So, it's always like this, right?
ということで、いつもこれでいるんでしょ?
Yeah.
うん
It's Shifuku, isn't it?
しふくですよね
Well, I guess I've already done it.
じゃあ、俺はもう、やり遂げたということで
Next.
次ですね
Miko dwarf.
みこ小族
Mikokozoku?
みこ小族?
It's Miko, isn't it?
みこさんだよね
I'm scared of wearing that white one underneath.
あの白の、着て下がこわくなってます
You can find them in shrines and such.
神社とかにね、いるやつですね
Miko dwarf.
みこ小族
I'm wearing a cat costume.
ネココスっていうのが着てますね
I put on cat ears.
ネコ耳つけた
Isn't it some kind of cute one with cat ears?
ネコ耳つけた系の、なんかあのかわいい系のやつじゃないですか
But it looks good on you.
でも、似合いそうだよね
But you look good no matter what you wear.
でも、君は何着ても似合いそうだよね
That's good too.
それもいいですね
Cat tribe.
ネコ小族
It's not a cat tribe.
ネコ小族じゃねえや
Miko Kozoku's cat costume.
みこ小族のネココス
Oh, I'm going to put cat ears on Miko.
あ、みこさんにネコ耳つけるんだ
That's different, that's it.
別だよ、それは
Oh, no?
あ、別?
I've never seen Miko like that.
そんなみこさん見たことないですよ
Ah, with Miko Kozoku.
あ、みこ小族と
Mikokozoku is Mikokozoku.
みこ小族はみこ小族
So, Nekokosu is Nekokosu.
で、ネココスはネココス
What the old man just said is a mixture of both.
今、おじさんが言ったのは、その両方が混ざっちゃったんですよ
That's a mistake.
間違いです
It's just a mistake.
ただの間違いです
Yes, next.
はい、では次
I guess this happens often.
これはよくあるんじゃないかな
There's something called erotic anime cosplay coming up.
アニメ系のエロいコスプレっていうのが来てるんですけど
However, unfortunately, I don't understand anything about uncle anime.
ただ、これ残念ながら、おじさんアニメ系全く分かんないんで
It happens sometimes.
たまにいるんですよ
There are some people who ask me which corner is Shimakaze cosplay,
島風のコスプレでどのコーナーって言ってくる人いるんだけど、
I'm talking about what Shimakaze is.
島風って何ですかっていう話なんですね
What is Shimakaze?
島風って何?
What about this?
これのこと?
I don't know.
わからない
Aren't they wearing clothes from the islands?
島々の服着てるんじゃない?
On the other hand?
そういう逆に?
Uncle, I don't understand, that's what you said.
おじさん分かんないんだよ、そんなこと言われてんの
But he's an old man.
でも、おっさんだからさ
I don't understand.
分かんないです
Erotic anime cosplay.
アニメ系のエロいコスプレ
What is erotic anime cosplay?
アニメ系のエロいコスプレってどういうの?
I feel like Shizuka-chan.
静香ちゃんみたいな感じ
Erotic anime cosplay.
アニメ系のエロいコスプレ
Do you know anything?
何か知ってる?
If you're famous...
有名だと、あの...
That's what I just said, right?
今言ったあれでしょ、カンコレだとか
Or like Hancock from One Piece.
とか、ワンピースのハンコックみたいな、
A little bit about Muramoto.
ちょっと村元があいたやつとか
Sorry, I have no idea.
ごめん、全く分かんないわ
Can I have you do something that you understand?
おじさんの分かるやつにしてもらっていい?
Like Maizing Machiko Sensei.
マイチングマチコ先生とかさ
It's old.
古いですよ
But erotic anime cosplay.
でもアニメ系のエロいコスプレ
Ram-chan and those annoying guys.
うるせえ奴らのラムちゃんとかさ、
Because that's all I know.
そういうのしか知らないから
That's a little erotic too.
それもちょっとエロいですね
That's all I know.
そういうのしか知らないんですよ
In terms of age.
年齢的に
Ram-chan is fine.
ラムちゃんいい
real?
ほんと?
It's Ram-chan.
ラムちゃんね
I don't have it though.
持ってないけどね
Well, maybe I'll do it someday.
じゃあ、もしかしたらいずれやるかもしれないんでね
Next up, cheerleaders.
次はですね、チアガール
Like ponytails, or twintails.
ポニーテール、オア、ツインテールみたいな
I see.
なるほど
What do you think?
どうですか、それ
I'll think about it for a moment.
ちょっと考えますね
It looks good on you, cheerleader.
似合いそうだよね、チアガールね
It's definitely cute, isn't it?
絶対可愛いでしょ
It's a pain to tie.
結ぶのがめんどいんですよね
picture?
え?
To tie it.
結ぶのが
Is it a pain to tie?
結ぶのがめんどいの?
yes.
はい
What do you mean by troublesome?
めんどいってどういうこと?
My bangs are long now.
今、私長いじゃないですか、前髪が
It's long, it's long.
長いですね、長いですね
That kind of thing goes better with short bangs after all.
ああいうのって、やっぱり短い前髪の方が入るんですよ
Ah, shorter bangs are better.
ああ、前髪が短い方が
Yes, it looked a bit like a loli.
そう、ちょっとロリっぽくした
I see.
なるほどね
Indeed, it might be so, if you ask me.
確かにね、そうかもしれない、そう言われてみれば
If you ask me if it suits me.
似合うかどうかって言われたら
Don't you know?
わかんない?
I see.
そうか
I've received various Luce Cases,
いろいろリュケースもらってるんで、
My uncle has brought a lot of things with him, just in case.
おじさんは一応ね、いろいろ持ってきてはいるので、
It's up to Natsumi to decide what to wear.
何を着るかは夏みちゃん次第ということで、
There's something like that, since I'm a cheerleader.
一応そういうのもありますよ、チアガールということでね
Yes, next.
はい、次です
Joysan Hakui Nurse.
ジョイッサン・ハクイ・ナース
This is a hospital series.
これなんか病院シリーズですね
What do you think?
どうですか?
Yeah, it's totally fine.
うん、全然いい
There are some plays like that.
なんかそういうプレイあるよね
Look, she's dressed like a nurse.
なんか ほ ら、ナースの格好してさ
Yeah, yeah, it's super electoral like this.
うんうん、こうやって超選挙系でね
Yes, that's right, there is such a thing.
そうそうそう、そういうのあるじゃね
I think that kind of thing is good.
そういうのもいいかなと
Well, I also wear a case like that.
まあ、そういうリュケースも着てますよと
Yes, next time.
はい、次ね
Race queen.
レースクイーン
This suits you, doesn't it?
これは似合うね、君はね
Because it's thin.
細いからね
That's so cool, isn't it?
ピチピチのあれですよね
Yeah, I mean, I'm a race queen.
うん、ピチピチっていうか、レースクイーン
Next up, men's dress shirts.
次はね、男物のワイシャツ
This is erotic.
これエロいっすね
これはエロいよね
It's baggy.
ダボダボのね
Dabo Dabo.
ダボダボの
Just one dress shirt.
なんかワイシャツ1枚でさ
Isn't it erotic?
エロくない?
Yeah yeah yeah.
うん うんうん
It's a dream, isn't it?
夢だね、それね
If such a child were to wake up in the morning and make miso soup at Daisho, he would get married.
朝起きて、そんな子が大所でお味噌汁とか作ってたら結婚する
I think I'll get married soon.
すぐ結婚すると思う
I think he'll propose soon.
すぐプロポーズすると思うよ
Seriously.
マジで
A dress shirt might be fine,
ワイシャツはいいかもしれないな、
This is it.
これはね
Also, don't you have glasses?
あとは、メガネっていうのがありません?
glasses.
メガネ
Just wear glasses?
メガネをかけるだけ?
Is that so?
なのかな?
I think it would suit a female teacher.
なんか女教師とかなら似合いそうな
A teacher.
教師ね
Even if you wear glasses, you see.
メガネをかけるんでも、ほら、あるもんね
Like the teacher I just mentioned.
いろいろその今言った先生とかさ
What else, people who wear glasses?
あと何、メガネをかける人?
I don't know.
分かんない
Is it big?
大いるとか
You guys might give it a try.
お前らはかけるかも
No, I don't know.
いや、分かんないけど
But somehow, as an image,
でもなんかやっぱり一番イメージとしては、
That kind of female teacher is dressed a bit harshly,
そういう女教師がちょっといかつい格好して、
I have the image of a strict teacher wearing strict glasses.
厳しい感じのメガネかけた厳しい先生みたいなイメージがある
That's why you're attacking Toriso-san.
それで鳥相さんを攻め立てるということですね
yes.
そう
I see.
なるほど
Well, well, that's fine too.
まあまあまあ、それもよろいですね、
surely.
確かに
But what about the teacher type?
でも先生系のやつって、何つうの?
I like people from Bonkyupon.
ぼんきゅっぽんの人がいいよね
My boobs are big.
おっぱい大きくてさ
My waist is too tight,
ウエストがキューってしまってて、
A girl with a big butt style is more
お尻ドカーンみたいなスタイルの女の子の方が、
I think that kind of thing is erotic.
そういうのエロいと思うの
Oh, are you coming?
あ、君こない?
what?
何?
Oh, sorry.
あ、すいません
But my boobs have gotten bigger.
でも私、おっぱい大きくなりましたから
Have you grown up?
大きくなったの?
Yeah.
うん
Did you make it bigger?
大きくしたの?
Yes, I did.
うん、した
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
あ ら、ちょっと楽しみですね
got it.
わかりました
So let's think about that for a moment.
じゃあちょっとそれも考えましょうか
Yes, next.
はい、次
There are now types of swimsuits that become transparent when wet.
濡れると透けるタイプの水着っていうのが来てますよ
A type of swimsuit that becomes transparent when wet.
濡れると透けるタイプの水着
Ah, there is.
あー、ありますね
White or something?
白とかの?
It's white, it's see-through.
白とかのね、透け透けのやつですね
That means you have to get it wet.
それを濡らさなきゃいけないってことですね
It's something you have to do in the bathroom.
お風呂場でやらないといけないやつですね、
That's it.
それね
I see.
なるほど
It's definitely erotic, but I don't know.
確かにエロいんだけどな、どうだろうな
Next.
次ですね
There are blazer-type uniforms for JK,
ブレザー系の制服、JKっていうのが来てますけど、
But I'm doing something, that's all.
でもなんかやってるもんね、それもね
Well, I did it, I'm sure.
まあ、やりましたよね、確か
Yay, yay.
やったやった
I'm a catcher because I did it.
やったからキャッカーだな
micro bikini.
マイクロビキニ
Micro bikinis are also coming.
マイクロビキニっていうのも来てますね
Micro bikinis, tiny ones.
マイクロビキニとか、ちっちゃいやつね
It looks like you can see her nipples.
乳首が見えそうなやつですね
This is also very erotic, isn't it?
これもエロいですね、なかなか
Next up is erotic underwear.
次、エロ下着っていうのが来てますね
Erotic underwear.
エロ下着
Do you mean sexy lingerie?
セクシーランジェリー系ってことですかね
Oh, I'm wearing a garter belt.
あー、なんかちょっとガーターベルト履いて、
Like.
みたいな
Also, it's an underwear series, but it's a cute one.
あと、下着シリーズだけど、かわいい系の、
Kind of like underwear-style cosplay.
下着風のコスプレみたいな系
It's a cute, underwear-like cosplay.
かわいい風の、下着風のコスプレだと
What do you think?
どうですか?
What kind would you like?
どんなのがいいですか?
What I'm saying now.
今言っているのが
Well, cosplay is totally OK,
えっと、コスプレ系は全然OKだし、
Micro bikinis are also OK, so what else happened?
マイクロビキニもOKだし、 あと何があったっけ?
nurse?
ナース?
Oh, it's totally OK to cosplay as a nurse,
ああ、ナースとかも全然コスプレOKだし、
And what about darugi?
あとは、だるぎ?
Darugi, this?
だるぎ、これ?
Dargi?
だるぎ?
It's called darugi.
だるぎっていう
There is something called casual clothes.
だ る ぎ っていうか、私服っていうのがあるからさ
This is hilarious.
これはキャッカリ
That's hilarious.
それはキャッカリ
So what should we do?
じゃあ、どうしようか?
What do you like?
何がいい?
What should I do with this?
どうしよう、これで
Well, for now, there are various uncles,
じゃあ、とりあえず、おじさんがいろいろ、
I'm wearing extra clothes today, so
今日こんだけリペース着てるから、
I brought quite a lot, so I looked at it a little later.
結構いっぱい持ってきたから、 ちょっと後で見て、
Decide for yourself, then.
自分で決めて、じゃあ
OK、OK
Well, let's put it that way.
じゃあ、そういうことにしましょう
Well, what to wear is a matter for later.
じゃあ、 何を着るかは、後ほどのお楽しみということで
Next.
次です
Play request.
プレイリクエスト
I want you to play like this.
こんなプレイをしてほしい
First, let me start with the NG one.
まず、先にNGのやつから言っておきます
In short, I'll tell you first what won't sell.
要は、売れないやつを先に言っておきますね
Scat, pee.
スカトロ、おしっこ
Unfortunately, this doesn't sell in the first place.
これは残念ながら、そもそも売れません
I can't.
できないんですよ
It doesn't sell.
売れないんですよ
Accident.
意外
I could make it, but it would be a drag.
作ることができるんだけど、脚下されちゃうから
Oh, what else?
あ、もう何?
From the site side?
サイト側から?
Because the site will take you down.
サイトに脚下されちゃうから
This is no good.
ダメです、これは
Is that so?
そうなの?
What's not good is poop and pee.
ダメなのは、とにかく、うんこ、おしっこ
Is it okay to pee?
おしっこもダメなの?
Blood.
血
It's the so-called fishing animal type, or rather, the torture type.
いわゆる漁獣系というか、拷問系
This kind of thing doesn't work because of the number of co-layers.
こういうのは、コープレイヤー数の問題でダメなんですよ
It doesn't sell in the first place.
そもそも売れないんで
So, I'm sorry.
ということで、ごめんなさい
It's from the nose down to the legs.
それはもう鼻から脚下です
So, I'm going back.
ということで、戻りますね
Play request.
プレイリクエスト
This is already impossible since I'm here today by myself.
これはね、もう今日ちょっとおじさん一人で来てる時点で無理
However, 3P and multiple plays.
なんです が、 3Pや複数プレイ
Double fellers and triple fellers are coming,
ダブルフェラー、トリプルフェラーが来てるんだけど、
This is also an old man, so if I have another chance, I would like to have it.
これもおじさん一人なんで、ちょっとまた機会があれば持ち欲しい
That's what I mean.
って いうことで
But can I do it?
でも、いける?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
No, I don't like it.
いや、嫌だ
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
Is that no good?
それダメ?
No.
ダメ
Then it's no good.
じゃあNGね
Yes, next.
はい、次
From here on out, I think it's normal or relatively easy to do.
ここからは、普通というか、比較的できるんじゃないかなというや
That's right.
つ ですね
Soap play.
ソーププレイ
What do you mean Matt?
マットってこと?
Isn't that similar to matte?
それ、マットとかのアワアワ系じゃないですか
You can make a fluffy type.
アワアワ系ができますよ
Can you do it?
できちゃうの?
That's wonderful.
素晴らしいですね
It's called Our Center.
アワアワセンターってことですよね
Uncle, I've never been to a soapland before.
おじさん、ソープランドに行ったことないものですから
Eh.
えー
Um, in shooting, in shooting like this,
あの、撮影では、こういう撮影では、
I had a soap girl tell me this when she came over,
ソープのお姉さん来た時には言ってもらったことありますけど、
I've never seen it in a store.
お店に一回見たことないですよ
Eh.
えー
Accident.
意外
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
Until this year.
この年まで
She says she has never been to a sex shop.
一度も風俗店に行ったことがないという
What, other than soap?
えっ、ソープ以外も?
Other than that.
もう、以外も
Health, delivery health, pinsal,
ヘルスも、デリヘルも、ピンサルも、
There's nothing.
何もないんです
He's a precious person.
貴重な人ですね
Isn't it amazing?
すごいでしょ?
Once again, I'm just filming this kind of sex.
もう一度、こんなハメハメばっか撮ってるんですよ
No, maybe it's because we're doing it here the other way around?
いや、逆にここでやってるからかな?
I don't know though.
わかんないけどね
Well then, soap play is a good idea.
じゃあ、ソーププレイがいけますね
What is fast play?
高速プレイってのは?
Fast play?
高速プレイと?
Something like speeding up your hands or something.
なんかこう、手とかを高速したりとか、
Legs or something.
足とか
Oh, ok.
ああ、まあまあ
Isn't it like handcuffing or something like that?
手錠をかけたりとか、そういうことじゃないですか?
It's okay, it's okay.
大丈夫、大丈夫
Can you go?
いける?
Yeah.
うん
Are you being attacked by a store while you can't move?
動けない状態でお店に攻め立てられるんです?
Yeah yeah yeah yeah.
うんうんうんうん
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Yeah.
うん
Lately, I've been paying a bit of attention to the shops.
最近ね、ちょっとお店に凝ってるところもあるんでね
I'll think about it some more.
もうちょっと考えますね
Second-rate.
次
Attack Torizo-san.
鳥蔵さんを攻める
This is what I always attack.
これはさ、いつも攻めてるよね
I'm doing it.
やってますね
always.
常に
I feel like Torizo ​​is always being attacked.
常に鳥蔵さん攻められてる気がするんだけど
Is it bad?
悪いかしい
hey.
ね
As always.
いつも通りですね
The rest is netli, netli,
あとはですね、ネットリ、ネットリ、
yeah?
ん?
Net Rika Lingime Fellatio is coming.
ネットリカリナメフェラってのが来てますよ
Net Rika Lime Fellatio?
ネットリカリナメフェラ?
That's called Cali.
カリって、あの
That's where the thieves are.
あの、奇盗の窪んだところですね
The odd thief and Kari.
奇盗とカリ
Yeah yeah, it's okay.
うんうん、大丈夫
You do that all the time, too.
それもいつもやってますよね
Well, I'm doing it.
まあ、やってるけど
Isn't that what you're asking me to do online?
それをネットリしてくれってことじゃないですか
Ah, I see.
あー、なるほど
I wonder what netori is.
ネットリってどういうんだろうね
Do you do it in a naughty, sensual way?
いやらしい感じに、じんわーっていう感じにやるんですかね
Yes, I can feel it while hugging you.
はい、抱きつけてながら、感じかな
It's so naughty.
いやらしいですね
Just thinking about it makes me cringe.
想像しただけでじんこ立っちゃうんですね
it is.
それは
Next, footwork.
次、足こき
Oh, nice.
おー、いいね
Does footwork feel good?
足こきって気持ちいいのかな?
I wonder what it is.
どうなんだろう
I don't have very good memories.
あんまり気持ちいい思い出がない
I once hit my nail and it hurt.
爪とか当たって痛ってくなったことがあるぞ
Well, I'll leave that to you.
まあ、それは任せますよ
There's a footjob coming.
足こきってのが来てますね
Also, it's side sex.
あと、横ハメですね
What is side sex?
横ハメって?
Isn't it like that? It's like lying down like this and having sex from the side.
あれじゃないですか、こう寝っ転がって横からハメるみたいな
Oh, from behind?
あー、後ろから?
That's right, the enthronement.
そうそう、即位って
Isn't that what you meant?
ああいうことじゃないですか
Well, that's part of the flow,
まあ、そんなのは別に流れの中でね、
You can do it.
できますからね
Also, dildo masturbation is coming.
あと、ディルドオナニーってのが来てますよ
Ah, it's the other way around.
あー、逆かでね
why?
なぜ?
I hate dildos.
ディルド嫌い
ディルドが嫌い
Do you hate that too?
あれも嫌い?
Don't like vibrators?
バイブも嫌い?
dislike.
嫌い
Basically, I don't like insertions.
要は、挿入系が嫌いなんだ
Something like Denma or Rotor that deceives children is fine.
電魔とかローター程度の子供騙しみたいなものが大丈夫ってこと
hey.
ね
It just means that serious sex toys are no good.
ちょっと ガチの大人のおもちゃはダメってことね
Or rather, is it a dildo or a vibrator?
っていうか、ディルドとかバイブだっけ?
I have no idea how good it feels.
気持ちよさが全くわかんないの
In the end, you have to move it yourself,
結局は自分で動かさなきゃいけないから、
Natsumi-chan, what feels good?
なつみちゃんどこが気持ちいい?
Does Cree feel good?
クリーが気持ちいい?
Cree and uh, Cree below.
クリーと、 あー、下だとクリー
The rest is breasts.
あとはおっぱい
Well, it seems orthodox.
まあ、オーソドックスな感じですね
Well, that's definitely not a good idea.
じゃあ、それはやっぱりダメですね
Both dildos and vibrators.
ディルドもバイブもね
That's a shame.
だ って、残念
Yes, next, exposure.
はい、次、露出
Exposed?
露出?
exposed.
露出
Because it's raining.
雨降ってるからね
Let's stop.
やめよう
I can sleep.
寝れる
Second-rate.
次
I'm asking you to do an embarrassing yotsumbai pose.
よつんばいの恥ずかしいポーズをしてくださいって聞いてますね
This is an embarrassing pose for a cosplayer.
これ、コスプレで来てもらって、よつんばいで恥ずかしいポーズ
Embarrassing pose while flowing slowly.
よつんばいに流しながら恥ずかしいポーズ
It becomes an image video.
イメージビデオになっちゃうんですね
It looks like Natsumi's image video.
なつみちゃんのイメージビデオみたいになっちゃうんですね
If you could give me a lecture.
レクチャーしていただければ
Is it your uncle?
おじさんがですか?
Uncle, can I give you a lecture?
おじさん、レクチャーできるかな?
It's like this.
こんな感じだよ、みたいな
Uncle, I don't understand anything like that.
全然おじさん、そういうの分かんないね
You see, I'm not interested in celebrities or idols,
あのほら、タレントさんとかアイドルとか興味ないから、
I don't watch gravure or anything like that.
見ないんですよ、グラビアとかを
Off too?
AVも?
I don't watch AV either.
AVも見ないです
Oh, really?
えー、本当に?
I don't know.
知らないの
Super unexpected.
超意外
That's surprising.
意外だよね
I think everyone probably thinks so.
多分ね、皆さんそう思ってると思うよ
It's true.
本当だ
As I said earlier, there's nothing in the entertainment industry.
さっきも言ったけど、風俗系一切ってことないし
Already on talent, idols, AV,
もう、タレント、アイドル、AV上、
I have no interest in it, so I don't know.
全く興味ないから、分かんないんですよ
So even if someone like you comes,
だから、あなたみたいな人を来ても、
I don't know anything about it.
全く知らないんですよ
It's amazing.
すごいんだよ
So everyone...
だからみんななんかね、その...
That Natsumi uncle is amazing.
あの、なつみのおじさん、すごいですね、
Like.
みたいな
I'll bring some amazing people with me.
何 でもすごい人を連れてきますねとか、
You say you know everything, but
何でも知ってますねとか言うけど、
On the contrary, I don't know anything.
逆に言うと、何にも知らないんだよ、
Really.
本当に
I asked about it later, learned about it later,
後から聞いてとか、後から知って、
It's like thinking, ``Oh, that's right.''
えー、そうなんだ、って思うような感じですよ、
everytime.
いつも
Well, that's okay, that's the story.
まあいいや、それはね、そんな話
Yes, I'll go next time.
はい、次行きます
Eye car cum.
眼車ごっくん
This one comes every time.
これね、毎回来るんですよ
Well, that's mostly true, but first of all,
まあ、大概そうなんだけど、まず、
As for the eyes, I have to touch up my makeup.
眼車については、メイクを直さなきゃいけないっていうのが
Yes, there is.
あります ね
If it's a girl.
女の子の場合は
If I'm going to do it, it's really the last time, and I'll stop like this today.
やるなら、もう本当にラストか、もう今日はこのまま止まっちゃう
You can't do it unless you have the time to say,
ぞ っていう時がないとできないですよね、
I'm sure.
きっとね
What do you think?
どうなんですか?
none.
なし
Are you saying cum?
ごっくんって言ってます?
none.
なし
Do you dislike sperm?
精子苦手ですか?
dislike.
嫌い
I hate sperm.
精子嫌いなんだ
That's not good.
まずいじゃん
Do you ever drink?
飲むことある?
own.
自分の
There's no way that's the case.
あるわけないでしょ
Right?
でしょ?
It can't be.
あるわけない
I don't like that.
嫌だよ、そんなの
You never drink.
絶対飲まないでしょ
Then I'll go to the next one.
じゃあ次行きますね
Manpe.
まんぺ
Manpe?
まんぺ?
Please tell me your story.
まんぺを聞かせてください
Ah, but that one.
あーでもそのやつ
If you do it with your back and let some air in, it will come out.
まんぺはバックでね、ちょっと空気を入れながらやれば出ます
So.
んで
Regarding Manpe, there will probably be some.
ま んぺに関しては多分出るでしょうっていうことで
We've been friends for a long time.
連続仲だし
I'm looking forward to Torizo's best performance.
鳥蔵さんの絶臨者に期待しています
Now it's up to you.
もうあなた次第ですね
Can I go?
行けますか?
Continuous means you can't skip it.
連続ってことはだって抜かないってことだよね
Yeah, just go ahead and see me again soon.
そう、もうそのまま行ってすぐまた会って
This really depends on Torizo-san's physical condition.
これは鳥蔵さんの本当に体調次第です
All this.
こればっかりは
Otherwise, I've been feeling a bit indie lately.
そういでなくても最近ちょっとインディー気味なんだよ
Seriously.
まじで
Well, it's a bit of a Hollywood course.
まぁちょっとホリウッドコースでじゃん
Well, I'd do it if I could, but it's probably not possible.
まぁ ちょっとね、できたらやるけど多分無理だろうなぁ、
I think so.
と思いますよ
Really, I think everyone is already slightly aware of it,
ほんとね、もう皆さんもううすうす気づいてると思うけど、
I can't do it because I'm an old man and I'm not young.
おじさんだからさ、若くないからできないんですよ
first.
まず
Yeah, but there are also some old guys who are really cool.
え、でもおじさんでもすごいく人もいますよ
Is that rare?
あれ、稀なのですか?
I think it's rare.
稀だと思いますよ
I haven't used it much since then.
それからもう今までよっぽど使ってないからですよ
surely.
きっと
Ah, I see.
あぁ、なるほどね
I use it too much in front of my uncle.
おじさんの前は使いすぎてるから
already.
もう
After all, it's been about 30 years since I lost my virginity.
だってもう童貞を捨ててから30年くらい経ってるわけだからさ
Well, I guess so.
まぁでもそうやね
They say if you overdo it, it won't come out.
やりすぎると出ないって言いますもんね
Well, that's right.
まぁそうだね
So it depends on your physical condition.
だからそれは体調次第ってことでね
Yes, that's next.
はい、次ですね
Please let me hear your fart.
おならを聞かせてください
Do you fart?
おなら出る?
Farting depends on the time and situation.
おならは時と場合によりますね
Really.
ほんとに
Sometimes when my uncle is fucking me, he puts a little effort into it,
おじさんたまにハメてるときにちょっと力入っちゃって、
There are times when it pops out.
ぷって出るときありますよね
Get out!
出るんだ!
There are times when I have to go out.
出ちゃう時ある
Like when I drank too much the day before or when my stomach feels loose.
前の日飲みすぎた日とか、お腹緩い時とかね
It sticks out a little.
ちょっとぷって出ちゃう
I'll cut that too though.
それとかもカットしますけどね
I guess it's on hold.
保留かな
I feel like I should come out.
出たらって感じ
It feels like it's coming out.
出たらって感じね
That's because when you say, "Yes, I'm going to fart," it doesn't come out.
それはね、はいおなら出しますよって言って出ないからね
That's true.
それはそうですよね
It makes me feel like some kind of comedian.
どっかのお笑い芸人みたいな感じになっちゃう
Also, there is a creampie pussy cuppa.
あとはですね、中出しマンコクパってのがありますね
Oh, cum inside me, cum inside my pussy,
あ、中出しして、中出しマンコクパして、
I think I'll put it out here.
ここに出すみたいな
Furthermore, there is one more thing.
さらにですね、もう一個あるんですよ
It's a different person, but there is a thing called creampie pussy masturbation.
違う人なんだけど、中出しマンコオナニってのがありますよ
Aren't you going to masturbate and masturbate while your pussy is creampied?
中出しマンコのままクパしてオナニにするんじゃない?
Why?
何で?
what?
何?
You can drink it.
飲んでもいいよ
No, it's just a feeling of legs.
いや、ちょっと脚感で
Feet feel?
脚感?
got it.
わかりました
So, I took a moment to read out the request.
ということで、ひとしきりリクエストを読み上げたんで
There are many things you can do and cannot do,
できる、できない、いろいろありますけど、
First of all, think about the costumes.
まずは衣装とかね、考えて
Also, when it comes to playing, let's think about it as we play.
あと プレイに関しては、やりながら考えていきましょう
Oh yeah, I've also received a few messages.
そうそう、あと、いくつかメッセージをいただいてます
message.
メ ッセージ
Want to hear it?
聞きたい?
Just in case.
一応
May I ask?
一応聞く?
Well then, you can go.
じゃあ、いけますよ
In a positive way?
ポジティブな感じで?
Yeah, I didn't prepare anything weird from the beginning,
うん、変なやつは最初から用意しなかったんで、
I.
私
OK、OK
Just in case, I'll come.
一応ね、いきますね
I love it.
大好きです
I've been rooting for you ever since, so I hope you'll continue to watch more videos.
応援してから応援してるので、これからも多くの動画をよろしく
please.
お願いします
I love you so much.
大 好きだって
Oh, hello.
あー、どうもどうも
More videos or more to come.
多くの動画か、これからも
Even many videos.
多くの動画だって
That's up to you, isn't it?
それはおじさん次第じゃないですか
I agree.
そうだね
It depends on your convenience.
都合次第だね
It depends on your uncle's convenience, right?
おじさんの都合次第じゃないですか
Yes, next time.
はい、次はね
Ah, this is nice.
あー、これいいですね
I have been healed by Natsumi's cuteness many times.
なつみちゃんの可愛さに何度も癒されてます
I'm telling you to do your best.
頑張ってくださいって言ってますよ
It's healing.
癒されてるんだって
No, you can't wear Dalvik like that.
ダメだよ、そんなダルビック着て
There are people who are being healed.
癒されてる人いるんだよ
why?
なんで?
This is healing, number one.
これで癒してるしよ、一番の
Well, it's kind of like being in a room.
まあ、いわゆるね、部屋にいる感じでね
She says her sexy smile is wonderful.
色っぽい笑顔が素敵ですって言ってますよ
The glasses look great on you.
メガネがとても似合いそう
Oh, is this the person from Biquest with glasses from earlier?
あ、これさっきのメガネのビクエストの人かな?
There you have it, glasses.
あったね、メガネ
Maybe so.
そうかもしれない
I don't know though.
わからないけど
Because sexy glasses are wonderful.
だって色っぽいメガネが素敵なんだって
Not sexy glasses.
色っぽいメガネじゃねえ
I think your sexy smile is wonderful.
色っぽい笑顔が素敵なんだって
Natsumi-chan, you have such a nice smile.
なつみちゃん、こう笑顔がいいよね、
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いよね
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
My uncle is also healed.
おじさんも癒されてますよ
Really?
本当に?
Why do you say it like that?
なんでさ、そういう言い方をするの?
That's strange, isn't it?
おかしいよね
Lately, I've been trying to live more and more,
最近ちょっとね、だんだん生きてくれで、
The thorns are getting stronger.
トゲがどんどん強くなってきて
Ah, that's right, thorns have grown.
あ、そうなんだ、トゲが生えてきちゃったんだ
Well, that just happens as you get older.
まあ、それは年をとるごとにそうなるもんですよ、
As for people.
人というのはね
This can't be helped.
これはしょうがないし
Second-rate.
次
She is very cute and beautiful and I love her.
とっても可愛くてすごく美人さんで大好きです
I love it too much.
好きすぎます
I'm sorry for saying something that made you feel bad.
気持ち悪いことを言ってしまってすみません
It's disgusting.
気持ち悪いですね
It's a lie, it's a lie.
嘘だよ、嘘だよ
But I'm rooting for you.
でも応援してます
A place where you will definitely be happy.
絶対幸せになってくるところ
I'm asking you to be happy,
幸せになってくださいと言ってるよ、
This person.
この人
If you want me to be happy,
幸 せ にな ってくださいと言うなら、
I want you to try your best.
もうちょっとね、頑張ってほしいね
to whom?
誰に?
To that person.
その人に
Oh, to this person?
あ、この人に?
Then I'll have you buy about 100 of them.
じゃあ100本くらい買ってもらおう
No, I'm going to give it a lecture.
いや、講座に振るごうのし
Ah, then please give me the course number here.
あ、じゃあ講座番号をこちらまで、
I'll put it out below.
下に出しておきますのでね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I was in a rush, wondering what to do.
どうしようか、殺到した
You won't.
しないだろ
In what sense do you want me to be happy?
どういう意味の幸せになってくださいなんですかね
For example, a good marriage as a woman.
例えば、良い結婚を女性としてね
Please get married and build a path to happiness.
結婚をして、幸せの過程を築いてくださいなのか、
I hope you earn a lot of money and be happy.
いっぱいお金稼いで幸せになってくださいなのか、
Isn't it?
あるじゃない?
No, definitely all the awards.
いや、絶対全賞でしょ
I see.
そっか
Well, well, no.
まあまあまあ、いいや
So, with that said, let's just say...
じゃあ、そんなことで、じゃあちょっと、
First, let's choose an outfit.
まずはね、衣装を選んでいきます
Look forward to it everyone.
皆さんお楽しみに
Yes.
はーい
Torejo-san, how are you feeling?
とれじょうさん、具合いかがですか?
No, I'm not feeling well at all.
いや、もう全然具合悪いですよ
I'll check it out in a bit.
ちょっとじゃあ診察しますね
Not at all.
全然、チンチンだ
Are you not playing chin chin?
チンチンかけてないですか?
Not at all, Chin Chin is in good shape.
全然、チンチンの調子が
Come on, put on a futon.
ちょっとじゃあ、布団して
It's not heavy.
重ましくないですね
Well, first I'll measure your pulse.
じゃあ、最初に脈拍から測りますよ
Is it your pulse?
脈拍ですか?
Isn't your pulse here?
脈拍ここじゃないですか?
Oh, here?
あ、ここ?
The pulse is here.
脈拍はここですね
I can't hear anything.
何も聞こえますね
Can't you hear anything?
何も聞こえないんですか?
He's dead though.
死んでるんですけど
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Where is the heart?
心臓ってどこですか?
Is it the heart?
心臓ですか?
As a human being, I think this is a good thing.
人間なんでこの辺もいいかなと思うんですけど
Are you okay, Torejo-san?
大丈夫ですか、とれじょうさん
I can't hear anything.
何も聞こえませんよ
Can't hear anything?
何も聞こえない?
Is it dead?
死んでるんですかね?
Wait a minute, let's take a look at your penis.
ちょっとじゃあ、おチンチンも見ますね
Do you also look at penises?
おチンチンも見るんですか?
The hospital here.
ここの病院は
Please wait a moment.
ちょっと待ってくださいね
It's a hospital that also looks at your penis.
おチンチンも見てくれる病院なんですね
There's something wrong with your penis.
これ、おチンチンに異常がありますね
Is your penis abnormal?
おチンチン異常ですか?
What condition are you in?
どういう状態ですか?
Maybe I haven't had sex for a while, maybe.
多分、ちょっともうしばらく、もしかしてセックスしてない
Is it?
ですか?
We have lots of sex.
セ ックスやりまくってます
Are you doing it all?
やりまくってますか?
So maybe that's why the function of the chin chin is already declining.
じゃあそのせいか、もうチンチンの機能が低下してますよね
Chin-chin function decreases.
チンチンの機能が低下
This is serious.
これは重症ですよ
Isn't there something you can do?
なんとかならないですかね?
Nurse, we have to do something about this.
看護師さん、これなんとかならないと
Shall we give you some special treatment?
ちょっとじゃあ特別治療をいたしましょうか
Oh, you're a nurse, but are you going to treat me?
あ、看護師さんなのに治療してくれるんですか?
yes.
はい
I'm a nurse here,
ここは、私、看護師なんですけど、
I have a medical license.
医師免許を持ってますんで
That's amazing.
すごいですね
それすごいですね
I see.
なるほど
Please give me some special treatment.
ちょっと特別治療をお願いいたしますね
In what way?
どういう感じで
Are you going to take it off already?
もう、もう、脱ぐんですか?
This is a treatment.
これ、治療なんで
Is it true?
本当ですか
Already, ah.
もうね、ああ
I'll make this depressed penis stand up.
この低下したチンチンを立たせますね、
first.
まず
First of all, I can't stand up.
まず、立てないから
There's nothing I can do about it unless I stand up.
立てない限りにはどうしようもないんで
I agree.
そうですね
Oh my.
あらら
What kind of treatment is this?
これは、これは何ていう治療方法ですか?
First, let Chin Chin stand up, and then bring it normally.
これはまずチンチンを立たせて、そこから正常に持っていく
So, it's a special treatment.
ように、 特別治療です
The first thing to do is to stand it up.
まずは立たせることからです
What is the name of the treatment?
何ていう名前の治療なんですか?
Hmm, if you say C, it's penis treatment.
うーん、Cって言うなら、チンポコ治療ですね
Is it a penis treatment?
チンポコ治療ですか
Even if you don't call it C, I feel like it's a penis treatment.
それCって言わなくても、チンポコ治療な気がしますけど
Well, yes.
まあ、はい
Is this what you requested earlier?
これは、あれですかね、さっきのリクエストのネットリカリノメフ
Is that what Era is?
ェ ラってやつですか?
Yes, I've already mixed it.
はい、もう混ぜてます
Kamosa, Kamosa, it feels so good.
かもさ、かもさ、めっちゃ気持ちいいっす
But this is a treatment.
でもこれは治療なんだよ
It's a treatment.
治療ですね
Well then I have to be patient.
じゃあ我慢しないといけないですね
It's been quite a while.
だいぶ経ってきましたね
Now it might feel good.
これで、もういい感じかもしれませんね
What is that doing?
それ何やってるんですか?
This is to check if the penis is normal.
これは、正常のチンコを確かめてるんです、
now.
今
Because of what you just did.
さっきのしたことによって
Yeah, it's gotten a lot better.
うん、だいぶ良くなりました
I heard something now.
何か聞こえました、今
I didn't have it on.
つけてなかったのに
I heard something.
聞こえました、何か
Because it's Espan.
エスパンなんで
I see, that's amazing.
なるほど、すごいですね
As expected of a teacher.
さすが先生
How are you feeling?
どうですか、具合の方は
I'm starting to feel a little better.
ちょっと元気になってきましたね
Well then, it's a little more.
じゃあ、もう少しですね
I think this looks pretty good,
これでだいぶ良い感じだと思うんですけど、
What do you think?
どうですか?
I feel like it's gotten a lot better.
だいぶ良くなった気がします
As expected.
さすがですね
What kind of treatment will I get after this?
この後はどういう治療?
After this, well, there's the ultimate weapon.
この後は、そうですね、最終兵器があります
Is it the ultimate weapon?
最終兵器ですか?
yes.
はい
There is a treatment that will definitely make you healthy forever if you do this.
もうこれをやれば、確実に永遠と元気になれるっていう治療が
Yes.
ございます
What kind of treatment is that?
ど んな治療なんですか、それ?
That's a trade secret.
それは企業秘密なんですけど
Do you want to do it?
やりますか?
I'll do it.
やります
Will I have to pay extremely high treatment fees?
ものすごい高額な治療費を取られたりするんですか?
It's expensive.
高いです
I'm a poor person, is that okay?
私、貧乏人なんですけど、大丈夫ですかね?
That's a bit of a problem.
ちょっと困りますね
Is it a discount or something like that?
割り引きとか、そういう?
Discount, this time it's special.
割り引き、今回は特別で
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Please excuse me for a moment.
ちょっと失礼しますね
Huh?
あれ?
Was it suddenly?
いきなりですか?
Is that kind of treatment?
そういう治療なんですか?
This is also a treatment.
これも治療ですね
It's part of the treatment.
治療の一環なんで
Does it look okay?
大丈夫そうですか?
yes.
はい
May I have a look?
ちょっと見せてもらってもいいですか?
How does it work?
どういうふうになっているんですか?
This, uh, nurse, this, bottom.
これ あの、看護師さん、これ、下、
Was it brain bread?
脳パンだったんですか?
now.
今
Yes, brain bread.
はい、脳パンです
everytime.
いつも
Are you always brain breading?
いつも脳パンなんですか?
Brain bread treatment.
脳パン治療
脳パン治療です
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいですか?
That's proof that it's working.
それ効果が効いている証ですよ
Is it working?
効いてますか?
Can I do this for a moment?
ちょっと、これさせてもらってもいいですか?
It's special.
特別ですよ
Is it special?
特別ですか?
Is there an additional charge?
別料金ですか?
Separate fee
別 料
It's gold.
金 です
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
What kind of treatment is this?
これは、なんという治療なんですか?
This is the final treatment for people whose penis doesn't stand up very well.
これは、あんまりおちんちんが立たない人のためにやる最終治療
is.
です
Is this the final treatment?
最 終治療なんですか?
I'm feeling much better now.
だいぶ元気になってきましたよ
That's nice.
いいですね
That's the feeling.
その気持ちですよ
circle
わ
Wow, that's amazing.
ー、 すごい
It's still a beautiful pussy.
相変わらず綺麗なおまんこですね
Do you work at home?
家の仕事してます?
I'm doing work at home.
家の仕事をしてますよ
It's amazing, it sticks to you.
すごい、吸い付いてきますよ
It will stick to you.
吸い付いてきますよ
I'm sorry you had to go through this kind of treatment.
すみませんね、こんな治療までしていただいて
I'm sorry.
申し訳ないですね
back?
バック?
Yes, normally in the back.
はい、普通にバックで
Oh, are you a manpe?
お、マンペですか?
Manpe, right now.
マンペですね、今の
Is it your current manpe?
今のマンペですか?
It's out.
出ましたね
Don't you fart?
おならは出ないんですか?
I haven't farted yet.
おならはまだ出ないです
Is it a manpe for now?
とりあえずマンペですか?
There's a lot of manpe.
結構マンペが出ますね
I'm feeling really good now.
もうさ、めっちゃ元気です
Good for you.
よかったね
Do you always do this kind of treatment?
いつもこんな治療するんですか?
No, I won't.
いや、しませんよ
Don't you?
しないんですか?
Is this a special treatment?
これ特別治療ですか?
Yes, it is a special treatment.
そう、特別治療です
Kango-san, you can't see anything because of your hair.
かんごさん、髪の毛で何も映ってないですよ
You can't see anything because of the hair.
髪の毛で何も映ってないですよ
Mr. Kango.
かんごさん
What happened?
どうしたんですか?
Mr. Kango.
かんごさん
Another oral treatment.
さっきのお口の治療、もう一回
Oral treatment?
お口の治療ですか?
Oral treatment is incredibly effective.
お 口の治療、あれがすごい効くんで
That's really effective.
あれがすごい効くんですよ
There was a request for Gansha.
リクエストでガンシャってのありましたけど
Gansha.
ガンシャ
There was, though.
ありましたけど
What do you think?
どうですか?
No.
ダメ
sorry.
すみません
My health has improved tremendously.
ものすごい元気になってきてしまいましてですね
It looks like something's coming out.
なんか出そうなんです
I feel like I'm about to come out.
なんか 出ちゃいそうなんですけど
What do you do?
どうしますか?
At the end.
最後は
May I?
いいですか?
Please let me out soon.
そろそろ出させてもらって
Is it finished?
お仕上げかな?
Would you mind if I let you out for a little while?
ちょっと出させてもらっていいですかね
It's already been a long time.
もう長いんで
I've become too energetic.
元気になりすぎちゃったんで
It worked.
効きましたね
効きました
A lot of treatment.
だいぶ治療が
Kango, please let me hear the heartbeat of your pussy.
かんごさんの、このおまんこの鼓動を聞かせてもらっていい
Is it?
ですか?
You're saying something exciting.
なんか ドクドク言ってますね
Are you Kango-san?
かんごさんなんですか?
this.
これ
Something happened though.
なんか出ましたけど
It's proof of purity.
清浄の証ですよ
Is this clean?
これ清浄なんですか?
Have you recovered?
治りましたかね?
I'm healed now.
治りましたもう
Something in particular
なんか特に
I was so excited.
ド クドク言ってしましたよ
The teacher's mass uniform has become a sperm protector.
先生のマス服が精子守りになりました
Is this okay?
これもう大丈夫ですかね?
Discharge me.
私に退院して
You can do it now.
もうできますよ
Can I leave the hospital now?
もう退院していいですか?
Yes, even today.
うん、今日にでも
Even today?
今日にでも?
It was good.
良かったです
I started pulling something out.
なんか抜き始めました
Is it hot?
熱いですか?
It's hot.
熱いですね
Well then, excuse me, I'm leaving the hospital.
じゃあ すみません、私退院しますので
yes.
はい
Sorry, thank you very much.
すみません、ありがとうございました
Okay, welcome.
いいよ、こちらこそ
I'm sorry.
すみませんでした
thank you very much.
ありがとうございました
Okay.
いい よ
It's a sequel.
続編です
Just a moment ago, nurse, don't pretend to be a doctor.
ちょっとさっき、ナース、お医者さんごっことは言わない
What would you say?
なんて言うんだろうね?
What was that?
なんだったんだろう?
Clean.
清浄
Well, it feels like illegal treatment by a nurse.
まあ、ナースによる違法治療みたいな感じ
It's illegal treatment.
違法な治療ですよね
So, this is the second installment.
ということで、第2弾なんで
What is it this time?
今回は何ですか?
This time...
今回は...
What did you come for?
何を来たんですか?
I'm a cheerleader.
チアガールです
Cheerleader.
チアガール
Amazing, cheerleader.
すごい、チアガールだ
I don't understand at all.
全然分かんない
Can I have you stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらっていいですか?
Can I give you a little motivation?
ちょっとやる気出してもらっていいですか?
Look.
ほら
ほ ら
Cheerleader.
チアガール
Hey, have you ever been to something like that?
ね え、そういうの、あれ、来たことある?
do not have.
ない
First time as a cheerleader?
チアガール初?
Yeah.
うん
That's naughty.
エッチだね
Cheerleader.
チアガール
What's going on with this?
これどうなってるんですか?
That skirt.
そのスカート
Huh?
あれ?
What is that?
何それ?
It's on.
ついてるの
I don't feel like doing it.
ちょっとやる気ないじゃん
Why?
なんでよ
I don't feel like doing it.
ちょっとやる気ないじゃん
Is it on?
ついてんの?
It's on.
ついてる
Can I summarize this for a moment?
ちょっとあの、くるっとこう、まとめていいですか?
That's that, uh, what is that?
あれはそれがね、あの、何だっけ、
Um, pompon.
あの、ポンポン
Pon?
ポン?
Ah, this.
ああ、これね
yes.
そう
Without it, wouldn't it look like a cheerleader?
それないとチアガールっぽくなくない?
surely.
確かに
For now, try holding a tissue in both hands.
とりあえずティッシュ両手に持ってみる?
No, it's fine.
いや、いいよ
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
Okay?
いい んかい
No, but it looks good on me, after all.
いや、でも似合うね、やっぱり
As expected.
予想通り
Good, it suits you.
よかった、似合って
The size is also perfect.
サイズもぴったり
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
Uncle's can.
おじさんの缶
hey.
ね
Well, that's fine though.
まあいいけど
Well then, here's the second request.
じゃあ、ということで、第2弾、リクエスト
Well, you did quite well last time.
あの、前回結構やったからね
I agree.
そうですね
What did you do?
何やった?
Um, well, you played a nurse, right?
あの、まあ、ナースやったでしょ?
Nurse, uh, what?
ナースやって、えーと、何だっけ、
Where are you, Kito?
どこだっけ、きと?
Not.
じゃない
Ah, temporary.
ああ、仮
tentative.
仮
Lick it.
なめなめして
Temporary name.
仮なめ
Also, ascend to the throne.
あと、即位して
He ascended the throne.
即位した
What else?
あとは?
What else did you do?
あと何やったっけ?
You did quite a bit.
結構やったよね
I did quite a bit, though.
結構やった、でも
Well then, I think I should try something that I haven't done yet.
じゃあ、やってないやつをね、やっていこうかなと思うんです
But.
けど
Well, for now, I took the trouble to have you wear something like that.
じゃあ、 とりあえずですね、せっかくそういうの着てもらった
So, can I have you do a little chair leading?
んで、 チェアリーディングをちょっとやってもらっていいですか
hey?
ね?
Chairing?
チ ェアリング?
Chair reading.
チェアリーディングを
What is that?
何それ?
I understand that An-chan is like dancing like this.
なんか、あんちゃん、こう、踊りみたいなの分かるんだけど
Can't you do that?
できないですか、それ?
No, um, not at all.
いや、あのー、まったく
You are inexperienced.
未経験者ですよ
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Actually, I feel like I could do it if I wore something like that.
本当、そういうの着たらできそうな気がするんだけど
Is it no good?
だめなんですか?
Can't you?
できないですか?
I can't.
できないね
It can't be helped.
しょうがないね
So, this time, while responding to the request,
じゃあ、ということで、今回はリクエストに応えつつ、
Yori-san is going to do a stable toy attack.
よりさんがですね、安定のおもちゃ攻めをやっていきますよ
Toys I hate.
嫌いなおもちゃ
dislike.
嫌い
I don't like toys.
嫌いなんだよね、おもちゃ
Yeah.
うん
It tickles.
くすぐったいね
tickles.
くすぐったい
Breasts feel good, don't they?
おっぱいは気持ちいいんだよね
This prick stood up.
こっちのチクリ、立っちゃいましたよ
This is boring.
つまんないね、これね
Nowadays.
今時の
Turn it over.
めくったろ
Hide your breasts a little.
ちょっとおっぱい隠してね
Is that it?
あれですか?
Don't like this vibration?
この振動が嫌なんですか?
Yeah.
うん
No, I hate toys.
いや、おもちゃが嫌い
Don't like toys?
おもちゃが嫌いなの?
Yeah.
うん
Sorry for doing something I don't like.
ごめんね、嫌いなことやって
If you don't do it, you'll see the scale.
やらないとほら、尺が
Because there won't be enough shaku.
尺が足りなくなっちゃうからさ
Uncle will be leaving soon.
おじさんすぐいっちゃうから
No, no, no.
いやいやいや
I can't help it, this is all.
しょうがないです、こればっかり
Chestnuts are weak, aren't they?
クリは弱いんだよね
This is really disturbing.
ほんと邪魔だな、これ
This is a huge hindrance.
これすごい邪魔
obstacle.
邪魔
Kiccho
きっちょ
yeah.
ん
You look nice.
いい 顔してますね
What do you think?
どうですかね?
I'll check it out in a bit.
ちょっとチェックしますね
I'll check it out.
チェックしますよ
Oh, now it feels good.
ああ、もうね、いい感じにね
It's starting to feel good.
いい感じになってきましたね
Can I have you lick me in that naughty costume?
そのエッチな衣装でペロペロしてもらっていいですか?
yes.
はい
Well then, please do me a favor.
じゃあね、ちょっとお願いしますね
hey,
ね、
I'll sit here.
ここ、 私座ります
Oh, no.
あ、ダメだ
Very frozen in summer.
夏めっちゃ冷凍
No, no.
ダメだ、ダメだ
not go.
いかない
Well, that skirt, according to the uncle's plans.
でさ、そのスカートね、 おじさんの予定では、
I was planning to do it with my clothes on for a while, but...
ちょっとそのまま、着たままやる予定でいたんだけどさ、
It's no good if you're in that situation.
そういう状態だとダメですよね
Hey, this is it.
ね、これが
Well, I didn't expect it to turn out like that.
ね、そういう風になってると思ってなかったわ
I failed.
失敗したわ
Well, no.
まあ、いいや
So, let's take a look at that...
ということで、じゃあちょっとあの、
Can you slip out the bottom a little?
下ちょっと抜けますか
all?
全部?
Yeah.
うん
Because you can't have sex without pulling out.
だって抜かないとハメハメできないからね
I feel sorry for her though.
かわいそうだけどね
It's so cute.
せっかくかわいい
hey.
ね
It's already kind of moist.
もう なんかしっとりしてますね
Is that it?
あれですか?
Is that the phone you just called?
さっきの電話ですか?
It's a phone.
電話ですね
Uncle asked for another tasting.
おじさんは、再びテイスティングをね、
I will continue to do so.
していきますよ
I wonder what else you're not doing?
あと何やってないんだっけね
After?
あと?
You haven't done any creampie cuppa, have you?
中出しクパーやってないじゃない?
yes.
そう
But is that all?
でもそれだけ?
It seems like something could be done.
なんかできそうなのはそうだね
Really beautiful.
ほんときれい
Isn't it a good thing to have a beautiful pussy?
おまんこきれいって得じゃない?
Is that so?
そうなの?
Isn't that true?
そんなことない?
There's nothing special about it compared to other menu items.
他メニューとは特にない
Because they'll definitely say it.
だって絶対言われるじゃん
Will you never be told that your pussy is beautiful?
絶対おまんこきれいだねって絶対言われない?
I agree.
そうだね
I'm getting really wet.
なんかすごい濡れてきた
Nice tasting.
ナイステイスティング
It's erotic.
エロいですね
This is this.
これはこれ
No.
ダメだ
da
ダ
It's me.
メ だ
This is tough.
これは大変だ
hot.
熱い